<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Alimjan Mettursun</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Alimjan Mettursun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dansk Scanning A/S - WebLager</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/weblager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/weblager/</guid>
      <description>WebLager has been developed as desired and in close dialogue with building case handlers and other stakeholders in the municipalities around the country. It helps to ensure a relevant and usable surface for managing and using the archive in everyday life.
Technical role: Full-stack developer (Remote)
Features
 Font-end &amp;amp; back-end development by GWT (Google Web Toolkit) Unlock locked user status Search documents Download documents Auto-complete search by street names, municipalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay global localization &amp; automation system</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/ebay-localization-playform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/ebay-localization-playform/</guid>
      <description>Technical roles
 Back-end developer Test automation engineer  Back-end development
 Work status sync up between JIRA Multiple device localizationn pipeline automation Extend Jenkins Test result stats Automatic screenshot taking Screenshot editing and syncing Batch upload &amp;amp; download screenshots  Automated testing
 eBay website automated test script writing and screenshot outputting StubHub (ticket exchange company owned by eBay) Android &amp;amp; iOS APP automation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oral English practicing social media APP</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/language_learning_app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/language_learning_app/</guid>
      <description>Roles
 Boss man Full-stack developer  APP Features
 Sign in with WeChat Show geographical locations of signup users on the home screen Voice chat capability Natural language processing Speech to text conversion Analysing texts Possible answer suggession to a question Pay for membership  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft global localization &amp; automation platform</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/microsoft_localization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/microsoft_localization/</guid>
      <description>Technical roles
 Back-end developer Automation tool develope  Major responsibilities
 Microsoft global localization website back-end development Automated testing tools development (Web, Android and iOS) Language translation tool development for 52 different languages Pseduo translation generator Automoation platform monitoring tool. Whenever the tool crashes, monitoring feature sends Email to the developer with the bug specification  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O2O platform for kid&#39;s education of music</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/kids_education_of_music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/kids_education_of_music/</guid>
      <description>Music education platform that connects parents with music teachers. We offer two versions of this APP, one is for learners (kids), another is for teachers. Parents/students book classes of their prefered instruments, talk to teachers to decide the teaching time and avanue. Teachers give instant feedbacks to students.
Technical Roles
 Full-stack engineer  Application Features
 Instant messaging between student and teacher Curriculum generation Teachers suggession capability Instruments suggession capability WeChat &amp;amp; AliPay payment capability Book class capability  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team-based work management application</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/team_organizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/team_organizer/</guid>
      <description>A team-based work management mobile application designed to help teams organize, track, and manage their work. Helps team players manage their tasks, and communicate with colleagues. Helps team leaders assign tasks, track work progress and capacity of the team, and generate the weekly/monthly work report.
Roles
 Team leader Android developer  Application Features
 Sign up with WeChat Send/receive Emails with attachments Manage contact list Manage team assginments Upload/download files Review pictures Authentication Roles and privilages  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>