<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Javascript on Alimjan Mettursun</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Javascript on Alimjan Mettursun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dansk Scanning A/S - WebLager</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/weblager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/weblager/</guid>
      <description>WebLager has been developed as desired and in close dialogue with building case handlers and other stakeholders in the municipalities around the country. It helps to ensure a relevant and usable surface for managing and using the archive in everyday life.
Technical role: Full-stack developer (Remote)
Features
 Font-end &amp;amp; back-end development by GWT (Google Web Toolkit) Unlock locked user status Search documents Download documents Auto-complete search by street names, municipalities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eBay global localization &amp; automation system</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/ebay-localization-playform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/ebay-localization-playform/</guid>
      <description>Technical roles
 Back-end developer Test automation engineer  Back-end development
 Work status sync up between JIRA Multiple device localizationn pipeline automation Extend Jenkins Test result stats Automatic screenshot taking Screenshot editing and syncing Batch upload &amp;amp; download screenshots  Automated testing
 eBay website automated test script writing and screenshot outputting StubHub (ticket exchange company owned by eBay) Android &amp;amp; iOS APP automation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>O2O platform for kid&#39;s education of music</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/kids_education_of_music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/kids_education_of_music/</guid>
      <description>Music education platform that connects parents with music teachers. We offer two versions of this APP, one is for learners (kids), another is for teachers. Parents/students book classes of their prefered instruments, talk to teachers to decide the teaching time and avanue. Teachers give instant feedbacks to students.
Technical Roles
 Full-stack engineer  Application Features
 Instant messaging between student and teacher Curriculum generation Teachers suggession capability Instruments suggession capability WeChat &amp;amp; AliPay payment capability Book class capability  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>